Reptiles are found on all the continents of the world except Antarctica.
除南极洲外，世界各地都有爬行动物。
There are four main types of reptiles: lizards and snakes, crocodiles and alligators, turtles and tortoises, and tuatara, which are only found in New Zealand.
爬行动物主要有四类：蜥蜴和蛇、鳄鱼和短吻鳄、海龟和陆龟，以及仅生活在新西兰的喙头蜥。
Each reptile has its own distinct features.
每种爬行动物都有自己独特的特征。
Snakes are reptiles which do not have limbs.
蛇是没有四肢的爬行动物。
The shell of a tortoise is part of its skeleton on the outside of its body.
陆龟的壳是长在体外的骨骼的一部分。
It is called an exoskeleton.
这叫做外骨骼。
A veiled chameleon has its own distinct features.
高冠变色龙也有自己独特的特征。
Some species of lizard drop their tails to escape predators.
有些蜥蜴会断尾逃跑，躲避捕食者。
Some reptiles live on land, while others like crocodiles spend much of their time in the water.
有些生活在陆地，有些如鳄鱼大部分时间在水里。
All reptiles have lungs and need air to breathe.
所有爬行动物都有肺，需要空气才能呼吸。
Reptiles are cold-blooded, which means they cannot control their body temperature.
爬行动物是冷血动物，不能自己调节体温。
Most reptiles lay eggs, but some reptiles such as skinks give birth to live young.
大多数产卵，但有些石龙子直接生下幼崽。
Most reptiles are carnivores and eat meat.
大多数爬行动物是食肉动物。
Turtles and tortoises are mostly herbivores.
海龟和陆龟大多是食草动物。